Guide to the Nasri Fuleihan Collection AD.MC.056
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Nasri Fuleihan Collection
  - Two women and a man on carriage. (linked ref339, 341)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref370; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4 X 6.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Women; Horses; Animals; Carriages/Coaches; Group Portraits
  - Portrait of a man standing outdoors., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref371; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.9 X 7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Individual Portraits
  - Portrait of a woman and a child sitting on grass., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref372; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.7 X 5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Women; Children; Girls; Group Portraits
  - Men standing in front of tents., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref373; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Tents; Group Portraits; Hats; Regional/National Dress
  - Portrait of Nasri Fuleihan with stamps from the Cairo passport office., Circa 1919s; ref376; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.6 X 4.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cairo, Egypt; English Writing; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Passport/ID card; Men; Facial Hair; Postal Stamps; Individual Portraits
  - A man standing in front of a tent., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref377; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Portrait of a man in a room., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref378; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.5 X 4.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair
  - Faded portrait of a man., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref379; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.3 X 6.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Individual Portraits; Men; Studio Photography
  - A dog outdoors., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref380; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.1 X 5.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Dogs; Animals; Individual Portraits
  - A man sitting on a rock., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref381; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 5.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Individual Portraits; Buildings; Bow Ties
  - Men sitting beneath the awning of a tent., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref382; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.5 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Tents; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Turbans
  - Herbert & Huesgen Co. photograph envelope., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref391_000001; Herbert & Huesgen Company, 18 East 42 Street, New York; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.3 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Studio Photography; Jerusalem; English Writing; Printed Materials; Palestine
  - Herbert & Huesgen Co. photograph envelope., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref391_000002; Herbert & Huesgen Company, 18 East 42 Street, New York; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.3 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Herbert & Huesgen Co. photograph envelope., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref391_000003; Herbert & Huesgen Company, 18 East 42 Street, New York; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.3 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Hanania Brothers photograph envelope., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref392_000001; Hanania Brothers, Photographic Specialists, Jaffa Road, G.P.O. Box 72, Jerusalem (Palestine); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 X 7.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Studio Photography; Jerusalem; English Writing; Printed Materials; Palestine; Advertisements
  - Hanania Brothers photograph envelope., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref392_000002; Hanania Brothers, Photographic Specialists, Jaffa Road, G.P.O. Box 72, Jerusalem (Palestine); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 X 7.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Hanania Brothers photograph envelope., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref392_000003; Hanania Brothers, Photographic Specialists, Jaffa Road, G.P.O. Box 72, Jerusalem (Palestine); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 X 7.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Portrait of a man standing by a building., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref399; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7 X 4.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Individual Portraits; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Buildings
  - A crowd gathered on a hillside., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref400; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Crowds; Agriculture/Farms; Landscapes; Children; Umbrellas/Parasols; Regional/National Dress
  - An archaeological site in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref401; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 X 6.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Jordan
  - An archaeological site in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref402; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 X 6.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Mountains/Hills; Jordan
  - A man with a shoulder bag (linked ref417) in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref403; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes; Men; Bags/Purses; Jordan
  - A man posing in a car (linked ref416)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref404; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Men; Individual Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Hats
  - Four people laying on the ground in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref406; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.2 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Landscapes; Hats; Group Portraits; Jordan
  - A woman holding a gun in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref410, 411, 412)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref408; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 X 4.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Women; Guns; Individual Portraits; Hats; Weapons; Jordan
  - A man holding a gun in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref407; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 X 4.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Guns; Individual Portraits; Weapons; Jordan
  - A woman holding a gun in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref408, 411, 412), Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref410; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 X 4.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Women; Individual Portraits; Guns; Hats; Weapons; Costumes; Jordan
  - Two women standing on a mountain range in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref409; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Women; Hats; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Group Portraits; Jordan
  - A woman holding a gun in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref408, 410, 412)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref411; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 X 4.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Women; Guns; Hats; Individual Portraits; Weapons; Jordan
  - A woman holding a gun in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref408, 410, 411)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref412; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 X 4.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - A building complex on a hilltop in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref442)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref414; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Buildings; Landscapes; Jordan
  - A statue in the Ashkelon/Ashqelon archaeological site (linked refs 128, 142, 143, 367)., Circa 1923 - 1930; ref415; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 X 4.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Ashḳelon/Ashqelon
  - A man posing in a car (linked ref404)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref416; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Individual Portraits
  - A man with a shoulder bag (linked ref403) in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref417; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes; Men; Hats; Bags/Purses; Jordan
  - Boats anchored by fortifications along a coastline in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref429)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref428; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Seas; Coast; Jordan; Landscapes
  - Boats anchored by fortifications along a coastline in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref428)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref429; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Palm Trees; Men; Seas; Coast; Jordan
  - Nazareth & Tiberias' written on an envelope., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref434; 1 Photographic Prints; 12 X 16 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Nazareth; Tiberias/Tabariyyah; English Writing; Printed Materials; Palestine
  - A man pouring water over another man's hands in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref435; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.6 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Water; Clocks/Watches; Fez/Tarboush; Jordan; Group Portraits; Hats
  - A view of a town in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref436; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Men standing in front of a wall in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref437; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Landscapes; Hats; Jordan
  - A man posing with a child and a horse in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref438; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 X 4.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Children; Horses; Animals; Jordan; Group Portraits
  - A crowd beside two cars in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref443)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref439; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.2 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Hats; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Cigarettes; Buildings; Crowds; Jordan; Group Portraits
  - Four men posing in front of tents in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref440; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Hats; Tents; Group Portraits; Landscapes; Jordan; Civil Engineering
  - View of a town in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref441; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Buildings; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Jordan
  - A building complex on a hilltop in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref414)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref442; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Landscapes; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Jordan
  - A crowd of people in front of tents in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref439)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref443; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Children; Boys; Tents; Crowds; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Jordan; Group Portraits
  - Shrubland., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref444; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations
  - Studio envelope of Zerounian Photographer., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref446; Zerounian Photographer, Opposite Post Office, Jerusalem; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 X 15.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    English Writing; Printed Materials; Studio Photography